Wait. ls this really worth it?
(Sheldon:)We've lived together for years
with nary an argument.
(Leonard:)Huh?
(Sheldon:)But we start talking about a table,
(Raj:)and suddenly we're
at each other's throats.
"Nary an argument"?
"Nary"?
That means "not one," or "not any".
(Sheldon:)Maybe instead of a table,
you should buy a dictionary.
(Sheldon:)I don't know if I won that,
but at least he's upset.
(Howard:)Check it out.
Magic wand TV remote!
(Howard:)Yeah, I can control
all sorts of stuff.
(Raj:)Did Bernadette think it was cool?
Not when I said "mute"
and pointed it at her face.
(Raj:)Let me try.
Channelis changeroni!
(Raj:)This might be my second
favourite brown magic wand.